http://www.phoenixurns.com/privacyverklaring

Birds and Butterflies Urns
Urns Nature, etc.
Privacy statement
Phoenix Urns website privacy statementGeneral Data Protection Regulation (AVG regulation)Legally required statementEvery company is legally obliged to place a privacy statement on its own website because of the General Data Protection Regulation (AVG). So you know why your data are collected and what happens with them. Below is our statement.Secure connectionWhen you contact us using the contact form, your data are encrypted and sent to us via a secure connection. You can recognize the secure connection by the green lock in the browser, or by the green address bar at the top of your screen. In this way we offer you maximum security and fraud or theft of data is excluded.The green address bar and / or lock is shown in all recent versions of Chrome, Internet Explorer, Safari and Firefox.PrivacyYour privacy is very important to us.All personal information that you provide to us is therefore handled with care. We hereby strictly adhere to all legal regulations that apply to personal data. Your data will only be collected if you give your personal consent. Your details (name, address, city, email address and possibly telephone number) we need for (consultation about) the execution of a possible assignment, and / or to be able to inform you about the possibilities for performing an assignment (thepreliminary consultation). Your data will never be provided to a third party, unless there is a legal obligation to do so.Upon request, you can view the stored personal data and you can have them changed or deleted by us. You can also request to receive a data export with data that we use with your permission, or you can indicate that you want us to limit the processing of personal data.We reserve the right to make changes to our privacy policy. It is advisable to consult our privacy policy regularly so that you are aware of any changes.If you have questions or complaints about the processing of your personal data, we are happy to help. You will receive the fastest response by contacting us directly, by telephone, by email or via the contact form on our website.Under the privacy legislation you also have the right to file a complaint with the Dutch Data Protection Authority against these processing of personal data. You can contact the Dutch Data Protection Authority for this.More information you can find on the website:
https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/en
(English)Contact: Phoenix UrnsHoutlaan 167 9403 EZ AssenThe Netherlandstel. +31- 6 111 51 434 email: info@phoenixurns.com
Copyright Phoenix Urns ®  |  privacy statement  |  disclaimer  |  Chamber of Commerce no. 04073185
Share by:
